export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 0 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['2','3','0','1'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 0 x 2 ?',
            answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 0 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 0 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['2','3','1','0'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 0 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 0 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['2','1','3','0'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 0 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['1','3','0','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 0 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 0 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 1 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['1','0','3','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 1 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 1 x 2 ?',
            answers: ['1','3','2','0'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 1 x 3 ?',
            answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 1 x 4 ?',
            answers: ['4','1','2','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 1 x 5 ?',
            answers: ['5','3','2','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 1 x 6 ?',
            answers: ['4','6','5','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 1 x 7 ?',
            answers: ['7','6','4','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 1 x 8 ?',
            answers: ['6','8','5','7'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 1 x 9 ?',
            answers: ['8','7','6','9'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 2 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 2 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['0','1','2','3'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 22,
            question: 'What is 3 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['0','1','2','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 23,
            question: 'What is 3 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 24,
            question: 'What is 4 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['2','0','1','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 25,
            question: 'What is 4 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','4','2','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 26,
            question: 'What is 5 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 27,
            question: 'What is 5 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['3','2','4','5'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 28,
            question: 'What is 6 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['0','2','3','1'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 29,
            question: 'What is 6 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['6','3','4','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 30,
            question: 'What is 7 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 31,
            question: 'What is 7 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['6','4','5','7'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 32,
            question: 'What is 8 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 33,
            question: 'What is 8 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['8','7','6','5'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 34,
            question: 'What is 9 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['1','3','0','2'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 35,
            question: 'What is 9 x 1 ?',
            answers: ['8','9','7','6'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 36,
            question: 'What is 0 x 0 ?',
            answers: ['2','3','0','1'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
]
